I am optimistic that um that relations
with Russia will improve uh Trump said
on Friday that uh his people are in the
process of coordinating a telephone call
with Vladimir Putin and that he and
Putin will meet soon after he takes the
oath of office that is always a good
thing diplomacy is always a good thing
but we can't say the same thing about
China I don't think that there's anybody
in government who's sincere about
improving relations with China so what
will make the Trump Administration any
different from the Biden Administration
why is it that
we're supposedly or reportedly preparing
for war with China when Taiwan is saying
wait a minute wait a minute we're not on
an on the brink of war with China why do
you guys keep talking about war with
China it's because we're the ones that
are instigating this uh this problem